{
    "subject": "resource/Juhi_Chaturvedi",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lucknow",
    "human_readable": "Juhi Chaturvedi was born in Lucknow.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9075146317481995,
            "question": "Where was Juhi Chaturvedi born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8652120232582092,
            "question": "Name the city where Juhi Chaturvedi was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5791256427764893,
            "question": "What is Juhi Chaturvedi known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4761742651462555,
            "question": "Is Juhi Chaturvedi an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46839794516563416,
            "question": "What is Juhi Chaturvedi's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3687301278114319,
            "question": "Has Juhi Chaturvedi worked in Bollywood films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3152884542942047,
            "question": "Has Juhi Chaturvedi won any awards for her work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27733114361763,
            "question": "What are some of Juhi Chaturvedi's popular films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24766699969768524,
            "question": "Is Lucknow a major city in India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2241041660308838,
            "question": "Does Juhi Chaturvedi write screenplays?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Juhi Chaturvedi was born in Lucknow.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7987_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Lucknow a major city in India?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7987_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Juhi Chaturvedi's popular films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7987_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Juhi Chaturvedi won any awards for her work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7987_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7987_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7987_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7987_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7987_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7987_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7987_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7987_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7987_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7987_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7987_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that the triple \"Juhi Chaturvedi was born in Lucknow\" is supported by the context information provided. This can be verified from multiple documents, including:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7987/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7987/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7987/re-ranker-msmarco/94.txt"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Juhi Chaturvedi was born in Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh, India. Therefore, the statement \"Juhi Chaturvedi was born in Lucknow\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}